<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivitiesCodeChallenge</string>
    <string name="scrollview_one">This is the scrollview</string>
    <string name="button_main_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="button_main_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="button_main_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="button_one_text">BUTTON #1: NFL NEWS \n\n\n\nKANSAS CITY, Mo. -- Just about the only thing that looked familiar about the NFL\'s long-awaited return Thursday night was the sight of Patrick Mahomes effortlessly leading the Kansas City Chiefs up and down the field. \n\n\tThe Super Bowl MVP threw for 211 yards and three touchdowns, Clyde Edwards-Helaire ran through the rain for 138 yards and another score, and the Chiefs began defense of their first championship in 50 years by beating the Houston Texans 34-20 on Thursday night before a socially distanced crowd of about 17,000 due to the coronavirus pandemic. \n\n\tTravis Kelce, Sammy Watkins and Tyreek Hill each caught TD passes for the Chiefs. They have won 10 straight dating to last season. That run includes a come-from-behind 51-31 victory over the Texans in the divisional round of the playoffs. \n\n\t\"I\'m proud of our players but I\'m also proud of our fans. They came out there. They were loud,\" said Chiefs coach Andy Reid, who claimed he didn\'t notice some booing from fans during a pregame moment of unity involving both teams. \n\n\t\"Obviously, our players, both sides of the ball and special teams , I thought they were solid,\" Reid continued. \"For the first game there were some good things that were done, some great individual performances.\" \n\n\tThe Texans\' Deshaun Watson threw a touchdown pass and ran for another score, but he also was under relentless pressure and was intercepted once. David Johnson provided the biggest bright spot for Houston, running for 77 yards and a score. \n\n\t\"There\'s a lot to fix,\" Texans coach Bill O\'Brien said. \"It\'s only one game. We have to improve pretty quickly. But it\'s only one game . We have to get back to work pretty soon and fix these things.\" \n\n\tThe world has changed dramatically in the seven months since the Chiefs hoisted the Lombardi Trophy in Miami. \n\n\tWithin six weeks, the term COVID-19 had become a part of everyday life, the disease killing more than 900,000 people around the globe. The death of George Floyd at the knee of a white Minneapolis police officer in May touched off the Black Lives Matter movement, which in turn has led to a summer of social unrest that has gripped the country. \n\n\tAgainst that backdrop came an NFL opener unlike any other: masks worn by everyone from fans to the coaching staffs; a series of videos raising awareness of social justice initiatives and encouraging the public to vote; and ultimately both teams locking arms in a display of unity prior to the coin toss. \n\n\tTo the relief of many, kickoff finally brought 4 hours of normalcy. \n\n\tThe Texans, who blew a 24-point lead against Kansas City in the the playoffs, struck first when they marched 80 yards for a touchdown. The elusive Johnson finished it off by scampering 19 yards to the end zone for a 7-0 lead. \n\n\tBut just like that cold January day, the red-hot Chiefs quickly overcame their slow start. \n\n\tThey tied it moments later when Mahomes threw a short touchdown pass to Kelce, then took the lead when they forced a quick punt and Mahomes found Watkins in the end zone. Harrison Butker capped the first half by kicking a chip-shot field goal that sent the Chiefs to the locker room with a 17-7 lead. \n\n\tEdwards-Helaire, their first-round pick, padded the lead in the third quarter. After ripping off an 11-yard gain early in the drive, the pint-sized dynamo out of LSU unleashed a wicked stutter-step before running 27 yards for another score. \n\n\t\"He\'s just another weapon I have in this offense,\" Mahomes said. \n\n\tThe Chiefs put the game away when rookie L\'Jarius Sneed picked off Watson\'s jump ball in the closing seconds of the third quarter. Mahomes was bailed out of a fourth-down interception by pass interference in the end zone, then he zipped a dart to Hill streaking across the field for a 31-7 lead early in the fourth quarter. \n\n\t\"We just trust whatever Coach Reid is dialing up,\" said Kelce, who finished with six catches for 50 yards. \"They do an unbelievable job preparing us and scheming up defenses and we just trust what they\'re doing.\" \n\n\tWatson threw a touchdown pass and ran for a TD later in the quarter to make the final score a bit more respectable. \n\n\t\"It was a little different but the fans did what they did for their home team and that was pretty much it,\" Watson said. \"We just got to continue to do our job, find the rhythm, get guys on the same page and that\'s pretty much it.\"</string>
    <string name="button_two_text">BUTTON #2: MLB NEWS \n\n\n\nBauer outduels Darvish as Reds blank Cubs 3-0 \n\nCHICAGO -- Trevor Bauer tossed three-hit ball into the eighth inning to outpitch Chicago Cubs ace Yu Darvish and lift the Cincinnati Reds to a 3-0 victory Wednesday night. \n\n\tMike Moustakas hit a three-run homer in the first inning as Darvish\'s seven-start winning streak was snapped. \n\n\tBauer (4-3) struck out 10 and walked none in 7 2/3 innings while tying his season high with 112 pitches. The right-hander dropped his three previous starts, including a 3-0 loss to Darvish on Aug. 29 in Cincinnati. \n\n\t\"That was fun to watch,\" Cincinnati manager David Bell said. \"We needed a win and he did it against a good team. \n\n\t\"In a game like this, when you have two of the best (pitchers) in baseball, there was something a little bit different about Trevor. He rose to the occasion.\" \n\n\tBauer allowed just one hit -- a leadoff single in the fifth by Victor Caratini -- through seven innings. In the eighth, Bauer gave up a one-out single to Jason Heyward and was pulled after Ildemaro Vargas singled with two outs to put runners on the corners. \n\n\tLucas Sims got Ian Happ to line out to second, ending the threat. \n\n\tRaisel Iglesias worked the ninth for his sixth save. \n\n\t\"He really established his heater,\" Cubs first baseman Anthony Rizzo said of Bauer. \"He was locating it really well first time around and he started mixing in everything else the second, third time around. He\'s a really good pitcher and he was on tonight.\" \n\n\tDarvish (7-2) allowed three runs and two hits in six innings, walking three and striking out nine. All three runs and both hits came in the first inning. After that, the right-hander retired 16 of the final 17 batters he faced. The only blemish was a two-out walk to Brian Goodwin in the fourth. \n\n\tDarvish allowed only five runs in 46 innings (an 0.98 ERA) during the winning streak. He entered leading the NL with a 1.44 ERA. \n\n\t\"I couldn\'t control my body in the first inning,\" Darvish said. \"I tried to figure it out, but I couldn\'t.\" \n\n\tDarvish had walked a total of eight batters during the previous seven starts -- compared with 58 strikeouts -- but issued back-to-back, one-out walks in the first. One out later, Moustakas took advantage of a hanging breaking ball for a three-run drive. \n\n\t\"As soon as Moose hit that ball, I said, `All right, I can make this stand up,\" Bauer said. \"That was the goal. That helped lock me in.\" \n\n\nHEYWARD RETURNS \n\n\tHeyward returned to the Cubs\' lineup after experiencing shortness of breath and light-headedness in Sunday\'s game against St. Louis. The veteran outfielder passed a series of tests over the last few days -- including multiple COVID-19 tests -- and was cleared to rejoin the team. \n\n\tHeyward was concerned Sabout possibly having the coronavirus after experiencing shortness of breath during his first at-bat Sunday. \"It came out of nowhere,\" he said. \"Yes, naturally, that was a big concern of mine, for sure.\" \n\n\nCLEMENTE DAY HONORS \n\n\tHeyward and the Reds\' Tucker Barnhart were named their team\'s nominees for the Roberto Clemente Award, which is given annually to the player who best represents the game in character, community involvement and philanthropy. \n\n\tJose De Leon and Michael Lorenzen of the Reds and Javier Baez and Victor Caratini of the Cubs wore No. 21 to celebrate Clemente Day. All players of Puerto Rican heritage are allowed to wear the number to celebrate the late Hall of Famer. \"Hopefully next year, we get to see everyone wear it,\" Heyward said. \n\n\nTRAINER\'S ROOM \n\n\tReds: LHP Wade Miley (shoulder sprain) threw a side session. \"I got a good report,\" Bell said. \"His next step may be to rejoin us. He\'s passed all the tests.\" ... LHP Jesse Biddle (shoulder) also continues to improve, but there\'s no timetable for his return. \n\n\tCubs: 3B Kris Bryant was held out of the lineup after being hit with a pitch on the left elbow by Tyler Mahle in the third inning Tuesday night. Manager David Ross said he decided to sit the struggling slugger as a precaution. \"Some guys like to push through,\" Ross said. \"He was pretty sore last night, so I wanted to take that off his plate.\"</string>
    <string name="button_three_text">BUTTON #3: NBA NEWS \n\n\n\nWelcome back: Lakers, LeBron headed to the conference finals \n\nLAKE BUENA VISTA, Fla. -- The Los Angeles Lakers are going to the conference finals for the first time in a decade, ending the longest drought in franchise history. \n\n\tLeBron James is going there for the first time since 2018. For him, that also qualifies as ending a drought. \n\n\tJames scored 29 points and the Lakers wrapped up their first trip to the Western Conference finals since 2010 by topping the Houston Rockets 119-96 on Saturday night in Game 5 at Walt Disney World. \n\n\t\"It\'s the reason I wanted to be a part of this franchise, to take them back to a place that they were accustomed to being -- and that\'s competing for a championship,\" James said. \"It\'s an honor for me to wear the purple and gold, and for us, we just try to continue the legacy.\" \n\n\tKyle Kuzma scored 17 points, Markieff Morris had 16, Danny Green added 14 and Anthony Davis finished with 13 for the top-seeded Lakers. They will play either the second-seeded Los Angeles Clippers or third-seeded Denver Nuggets for the West title in a series that won\'t begin before Wednesday. \n\n\tJames is going to the conference finals for the 11th time overall -- six with Cleveland, four with Miami and now with the Lakers. It\'s his ninth time getting to this round in the last 10 seasons; the one miss in that stretch was last season, when his inaugural year with the Lakers fell apart because of injury and the team missed the playoffs. \n\n\t\"The opportunity to play for a championship, that\'s what we\'re all here for, that\'s what we all signed up for,\" James said. \n\n\tJames Harden scored 30 points, Jeff Green scored 13 and Russell Westbrook had 10 for Houston. \n\n\t\"Tough season for us,\" Harden said. \"Obviously, it didn\'t end like we wanted it to. Just got to figure it out.\" \n\n\tAnd now that the offseason is here, the speculation about coach Mike D\'Antoni\'s future will ramp up. His contract with the Rockets is now complete, the sides couldn\'t agree on terms of any extension a year ago, and he\'s been mentioned as a candidate for the vacancies in Indiana and Philadelphia. \n\n\t\"We\'ve got a great organization, great city, great fans, team\'s great,\" D\'Antoni said. \"I mean, everything\'s good here. We\'ll see what happens, but I couldn\'t ask for a better situation. I had four years and hopefully it keeps going. You just never know.\" \n\n\tIt was a tough end to a tough week for the Rockets. \n\n\tWestbrook exchanged heated words with a fan in the family section during the fourth quarter; NBA security asked the man, identified by ESPN as a brother of Lakers guard Rajon Rondo, to leave the game. \n\n\t\"He started talking crazy,\" Westbrook said. \"I don\'t play that game.\" \n\n\tHouston won Game 1 of the series and lost the next four. Saturday\'s finale came a day after Danuel House -- who averaged 11.4 points in nine playoff games this season -- was told to leave the bubble. An NBA investigation showed he had an unauthorized guest in his room for several hours earlier this week, and he missed the last three games of the series. \n\n\t\"It affected us,\" Harden said, who called the situation disappointing. \n\n\tThe Lakers ran out to a 33-11 lead, though Houston came right back with a 17-2 run to get within seven. The Lakers\' lead was 62-51 at the half after the Rockets turned 13 Los Angeles turnovers into 15 points, the biggest reason why Houston was still in the game to that point. Houston got within seven on a drive by Westbrook 2:09 into the third, and that was the last real gasp of hope for the Rockets. The Lakers scored the next 15 points, and the lead was 95-69 going into the final quarter. \n\n\t \"I\'m really proud of our whole team,\" Lakers coach Frank Vogel said.</string>
</resources>